Deploying apps to your Windows devices can be drawn through to a friend method.
You can add our use, for example, configuration manager, which is actually been installing
on-premises Windows server, or you can use TED by the software like PDQ.
But at the same time, we can't only use Microsoft Intune to deploy any kind of apps,
or any kind of software to your Windows devices.
If, for example, you want to deploy dot MSI software to your Windows devices,
let me show you how to do it from Microsoft Intune.
So, first of all, you need to go to your Microsoft, Microsoft Endpoint Manager admin center.
And from there, we need to click apps.
And from apps, we need to click on Windows because we want to deploy the apps
to the software to our Windows devices.
Next, we're going to select add. And from here, on that, the select app type,
we're going to click click, select app type.
And here, you can see we have, for example, how different kind of software can deploy,
like Microsoft Tris itself apps, Microsoft Edge, or even Windows Web link.
Well, I want to deploy the line of business app.
So, let's select that.
And here, you can see, it says, we can add a deploy dot MSI apps,
apps bundle, MSI X and MX X bundle.
So, if you had to plan this to Windows devices.
So, let me just click select.
And now, we need to select a package we want to include in this installation process.
Here, we need to click the app, package file.
So, just click on this folder.
And that's going to take you to your folder.
So, I'm going to go to my download.
And here, you can see, this actually is 7-zip.
Our menu is, it needs to be a Windows installer package.
Not a dot X-zip because it's not going to work.
So, just click open.
And here, we can see that the file has just been added.
And then just click OK.
So, now, you can see we have some extra information.
We can control the file at this moment.
So, I'm going to leave this other name.
I'm just going to leave that.
And for the description, I can control and modify it to your own test.
And for the publisher, I can just add, let me just add 7-zip there.
And it says app install contents.
It's going to be on user's contents and not on device.
We can actually switch to device.
But I'm going to leave this for user.
So, that users will have the opportunity to install the apps themselves.
Ignor app version, I'm going to say yes.
And also, command line argument.
Sometimes, you want to control it deploy some specific software using the command line
argument.
But you know, MXC totally include a package which allows the software to be installed on
devices silently.
We can actually show this as a featured app in a company portal, which means that the app
will be displayed in a company portal.
With then the user can actually install the app themselves.
But if we say no, then the app will be installed on other files automatically.
So, let me just leave that.
And then you can add some extra information about, for example, the developer, the privacy URL
of the software you are deploying.
But let me just click Nest.
And see on assignment, I want to assign it to all devices.
And then I'm going to click Nest.
Here you can see the summary of the apps you are going to deploy.
And now we can now click the create.
So, mind you, you can see it says application has been created at the moment.
Well, mind you, this app has been deployed to all devices, which has been recognized in Microsoft
Institute.
If I go to my devices, yeah, click all devices.
You can see we have to device.
So, now if this app, at the time of the app, it is devices on.
At the time, the app will be deployed to these devices.